{
   
   
    "q1":{
            "question" : "1. _______ Function displays the Latitude and Longitude in geoLcation in HTML5",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "showLocation()",
                "option2" : "showPosition()",
                "option3" : "both above",
                "option4" : "showStatus()"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
       
    "q2":{
            "question" : "2. In SVG, there is a support for event handlers",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "True",
                "option2" : "False",
                "option3" : "can't determine",
                "option4" : "none"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            }, 
    
    "q3":{
            "question" : "3. Canvas is able to draw the 2D graphics using _____",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "XML",
                "option2" : "JavaScript",
                "option3" : "HTML",
                "option4" : "XHTML"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q4":{
            "question" : "4. Which storage object is used for storing the data with no expiry date?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Session storage",
                "option2" : "Local storage",
                "option3" : "Mass storage",
                "option4" : "Stack storage"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q5":{
            "question" : "5. The manifest file is _____________",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Text file",
                "option2" : "HTML file",
                "option3" : "Java script file",
                "option4" : "xml file"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
    
    "q6":{
            "question" : "6. terminate() method in HTML5 is used for______",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "terminate everything",
                "option2" : "terminate all method",
                "option3" : "termainate a web worker",
                "option4" : "terminate program"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
     "q7":{
            "question" : "7. Which element provides a secure way to authenticate the user?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "keygen",
                "option2" : "datalist",
                "option3" : "output",
                "option4" : "input"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
       
    "q8":{
            "question" : "8. DHTML is the combination of",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "HTML, CSS",
                "option2" : "HTML DOM",
                "option3" : "JavaScript",
                "option4" : "all the above"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            }, 
    
    "q9":{
            "question" : "9. What is W3C?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "World Wide Web Consortium",
                "option2" : "world wide web corporation",
                "option3" : "world wide web company",
                "option4" : "world wide web company"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
    
    "q10":{
            "question" : "10. _____can open a link in a new browser window.",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "< a href =”url” new>",
                "option2" : "< a href =”url” target=”_blank”>",
                "option3" : "< a href =”url” target=”new”>",
                "option4" : "< a href=”url” target=”_parent”>"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            }
}
    
   
   
   
  